<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>yIGF.TW</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on yIGF.TW</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>&amp;copy; 2024 Youth Internet Governance Forum in Taiwan</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>yIGF.TW Second Online Meetup</title><link>/posts/20240808-meeting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>/posts/20240808-meeting/</guid><description>The meetup is scheduled for August 8, 2024, at 17:00 (Taipei time). Detailed meeting information is as follows:
https://u-tokyo-ac-jp.zoom.us/j/87923755622?pwd=DneQtc0AM2ZODMClAykbY9UkWwNN2b.1
ID: 879 2375 562
Passcode: 022751
If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us at organizers@yigf.tw. Everyone is welcome to join!</description></item><item><title>HE.NET Domain Outage</title><link>/posts/he-net-abuse/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>/posts/he-net-abuse/</guid><description>A few days ago, it was Independence Day in the United States, and many businesses took the day off.
However, on this very day, the domain name of major Internet Service Provider Hurricane Electric (HE, AS6939), HE.NET was suspended. This incident sparked significant discussion on the North American Network Operators&amp;rsquo; Group (NANOG) Mailing List.
The Incident On July 4, 2024, HE.NET was entirely suspended. The reason for this was that their domain registrar, Network Solutions, placed the domain in &amp;ldquo;Client Hold&amp;rdquo; status.</description></item><item><title>Article Submission Guide</title><link>/docs/how-to-post-an-article/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/how-to-post-an-article/</guid><description>In this document, you will find information about submitting articles.
Accepted Article Categories Articles must be related to Internet Governance, Technology Law, or relevant Public Polices.
Submission Process Contact Us:
Please contact us via email and include relevant information such as the article&amp;rsquo;s subject, draft, and author details. Submit in Markdown Format:
Our blog uses Hugo, so please submit your article in Markdown format. For those new to Markdown, we recommend using online Markdown editors such as StackEdit or HackMD.</description></item></channel></rss>