<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Authors on yIGF.TW</title><link>/authors/</link><description>Recent content in Authors on yIGF.TW</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>&amp;copy; 2024 Youth Internet Governance Forum in Taiwan</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ron</title><link>/authors/ron/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>/authors/ron/</guid><description/></item><item><title>TsungYi Yu</title><link>/authors/steveyiyo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>/authors/steveyiyo/</guid><description>TsungYi is a young man passionate about internet governance. He has been an APNIC and APSIG Fellow Alumni and has also been a speaker at TWIGF and the ICANN Engagement Forum.</description></item><item><title>Wen Yen Tien</title><link>/authors/wenyientien/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>/authors/wenyientien/</guid><description>Wen Yen is currently a second-year master&amp;rsquo;s student at the Graduate Institute of Political Science at National Taiwan University. Since April 2024, Wen Yen has been actively engaged in internet governance, beginning with participation in APIGA Taiwan and continuing with experiences at APIGA Busan, APSIG, and APrIGF 2024. These experiences have significantly expanded Wen Yen&amp;rsquo;s knowledge of internet governance and provided opportunities to connect with many esteemed experts in the field. Wen Yen also holds a bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Chinese Literature from National Taiwan University.</description></item><item><title>Tse Liang</title><link>/authors/tseliang/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>/authors/tseliang/</guid><description>Tse Liang is a graduate student studying at the International College of Semiconductor Technology at National Yang Ming Chiao Tung University. He is also interested and active in international relations regarding internet governence and technology. He is also an alumi of APIGA and a moderator/speaker at the ICANN Engagement Forum.</description></item><item><title>Wei-Ting HUNG</title><link>/authors/weiting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>/authors/weiting/</guid><description>Wei-Ting HUNG is a graduate student at the University of Tokyo&amp;rsquo;s Graduate School of Interdisciplinary Information Studies, where he is pursuing a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree. His research focuses on the regulation of the telecommunication industry in Japan, with a particular emphasis on zero-rating and network neutrality regulation in the Japanese telecommunication market.
Prior to his graduate studies, Wei-Ting earned a bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in computer science and information engineering from National Yang Ming Chiao Tung University in Taiwan.</description></item></channel></rss>